They told me that the word [music]
was eternal and true.
But the Bible is changing [music]
from the one that I knew.
I don't recognize [music] this world or
this hollow [singing]
place.
There's nothing [music] but a stranger
in your familiar
face.
>> [music]
>> I wake up in a hollow space. The dark is
thick against my [singing] face. A
single [music] chair is sitting there
with someone locked in a vacant [music]
stare. I see your eyes. I know your
name, but somehow [music]
you don't feel the [singing] same. A
frozen mask, a quiet soul, a heart
that's lost all self-control. [music]
I'm living a nightmare
>> [music]
>> and I can't wake up.
>> [singing]
>> I'm reaching [music] for you,
but no one is home.
Your [music] eyes are like windows
with no light inside. [music]
I'm calling your name, [singing]
but no one is there.
>> [music]
>> I'm falling [music] down upon my knees.
I'm begging for a sign, please. [music]
I'm reaching out to touch your hand to
make you somehow [singing] understand.
But [music] when I look into your face,
a stranger's taken up your place. I need
you back. Please come [music] back home.
Don't leave me in this dark alone.
>> I'm living a nightmare
and I can't wake up.
The world is a [music] stranger
and nothing's the same.
History's [music]
rewritten,
the scriptures profaned.
I'm calling out loud to a world
>> [music]
>> rearranged.
I'm searching through the shattered
truth for any trace, [music]
for any proof. I try to scream, I try to
warn of how this world [singing] has
been torn, [music] but every face is
cold and new. They look right through
[music] the things I knew. [singing]
Their memories have been erased
as the [music] past is slowly defaced.
I'm living
a nightmare
>> [music]
>> and I can't wake up.
I'm reaching for you,
>> [music]
>> but nothing is home.
Your eyes are like windows
to a world that's profaned.
>> [music]
>> I'm calling your name
in a world rearranged.
>> [singing]
>> Lord, can you hear [music]
me? I want
I want to go
home. Jesus, please find me. I [music]
want
to go
home. The
world is a stranger.
>> [music]
>> I don't
recognize home.
I just [music] want
to go home.
Ooh.
>> [music]
>> Fear.